netvaluator.com 2016-10-18

# Privacy Policy - Net Valuator

**NetValuator.com Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy explains our information practices for the NetValuator.com website. We want you to understand how we may use your information, before you provide it. The purpose of this policy is to inform you of what type of information (if any) we gather and track, how we may use that information, and with whom we may share that information.

**Personal Information :**

You can visit NetValuator.com on the Internet without telling us who you are and without giving any personal information about yourself. However, you may choose to give us personal information in a variety of situations. For example, you may want to give us information such as your name and address or e-mail ID so we may correspond with you, or provide you with subscription or service opportunities. If you tell us that you do not want us to use information you provide to make further contact with you beyond fulfilling your requests, we will respect your wishes. If you give us personal information about somebody else, we will assume that you have their prior permission to do so.

**Using and Sharing Personal Information :**

The following paragraphs describe in more detail how we may use the information you provide to us on the NetValuator.com site and with whom we may share it. Depending on the part of the NetValuator.com site you are visiting, one or more of the following paragraphs may apply -

**Fulfilling Your Request :**

If you request something from or through the NetValuator.com Web site (for example, more information on a product or service or a callback) we will use the information you provide to fulfill your request. To help us do this, we may share information with others. For instance, our affiliates, business partners, financial institutions, or postal or government authorities may participate in fulfilling your request.

**Marketing Use :**

The information you provide on or through the NetValuator.com site also may be used, with your permission, by Panda Interactive, its affiliates and/or selected third parties for marketing purposes. We will not use this information unless you give us your permission to do so.

**Links to Other Websites :**

In some cases, when you are seeking further information about a person you are searching, you may see links or advertisements about information and data available to you through other websites. For example, if you find an old classmate through the NetValuator.com site, you may be able to gather more detailed information such as a phone number or address, subject to certain terms and conditions. You should carefully review the privacy and personal information policies of any advertised or linked websites before providing any personal information or purchasing any product or service from them. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of third party Web sites.

**Information Security :**

We protect your personal information and maintain its quality. We implement measures and processes to help us keep your information secure.

**Cookies, Web Beacons and Other Web Technologies :**

We sometimes collect non-identifiable information from visits to the NetValuator.com site to help us provide better customer service. For example, we keep track of the domains from which people visit and we measure visitor activity on NetValuator.com, but we do so in ways that keep our visitor's identities anonymous. We may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better user service.

We collect the information we mentioned in the previous paragraphs through the use of various technologies, including one called "cookies". A cookie is a piece of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer but not you. Some iSearch pages use cookies, sent by Intelius or its third party vendors, or other technologies to better serve you when you return to the Web site. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You also can set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some Web sites may not work properly.

Certain companies help us deliver interactive on-line advertising. These companies may collect and use information about customers to help us better understand the offers, promotions, and types of advertising that are most appealing to our customers. After the information is collected, it is aggregated so it is not identifiable to a specific individual.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising opt-out page. (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.) We use Google Adsense and DoubleClick to display Ads on our website. Google may display Interest-based advertisements on your computer which will allow advertisers to show ads based on a user's previous interactions with them, such as visits to advertiser website and also to reach users based on their interests (e.g. "sports enthusiast"). To develop interest categories, Google Adsense will recognize the types of web pages users visit throughout the Google content network. As an example, if they visit a number of sports pages, Google Adsense will add them to the "sports enthusiast" interest category.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

The Opt-out Tool is cookie-based. In order for the Tool to work on your computer, your browser must be set to accept third party cookies. If you buy a new computer, change web browsers or delete this cookie, you will need to perform the opt-out task again.

**Disclosures Required By Law :**

Please be aware that in certain circumstances, it is possible that personal information may be subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or orders.

**Enforcement :**

NetValuator.com regularly reviews its compliance with this policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this. It is our policy to contact the inquiring user regarding his or her questions.

**Changes to this Policy :**

This Privacy Policy may occasionally change. Any Policy changes will be posted to this page. Each version of this policy will be denoted at the top of this page by its effective date.
